const quizQuestion = [
    {
        question : "Q1 : What country has the highest life expectancy?",
        a: 'Japan',
        b : "Hong Kong",
        c : "Canada",
        d : 'Germany',
        ans : "Hong Kong"
    },
    {
        question : "Q2 : What is the most common surname in the United States?",
        a: 'Miller',
        b : "Jones",
        c : "Williams",
        d : 'Smith',
        ans : "Smith"
    },
    {
        question : "Q3 : How many minutes are in a full week?",
        a: "10080",
        b : "12015",
        c : "9040",
        d : '24010',
        ans : "10080"
    },
    {
        question : "Q4 : What company was originally called 'Cadabra'?",
        a: 'Microsoft',
        b : "Samsung",
        c : "Amazon",
        d : 'IBM',
        ans : "Amazon"
    },
    {
        question : "Q5 : What country drinks the most coffee per capita?",
        a: 'Australia',
        b : "Bangladesh",
        c : "Finland",
        d : 'Argentina',
        ans : "Finland"
    },
    {
        question : "Q6 : What company was initially known as 'Blue Ribbon Sports'?",
        a: 'Nike',
        b : "Adidas",
        c : "Apple",
        d : 'Puma',
        ans : "Nike"
    },
    {
        question : "Q7 : How many bones do we have in an ear?",
        a: '1',
        b : "7",
        c : "5",
        d : '3',
        ans : "3"
    },
    {
        question : "Q8 : What is the world's fastest bird? ",
        a: 'Keel-billed toucan',
        b : "The Peregrine Falcon",
        c : "Hoatzin",
        d : 'Kiwi',
        ans : "The Peregrine Falcon"
    },
    {
        question : "Q9 : The Parthenon Marbles are controversially located in what museum?",
        a: 'The British Museum',
        b : "Palace Museum",
        c : "Vatican Museums",
        d : 'National Gallery',
        ans : "The British Museum"
    },
    {
        question : "Q10 : Which is the only body part that is fully grown from birth? ",
        a: 'Brain',
        b : "Nose",
        c : "Leg",
        d : 'Eyes',
        ans : "Eyes"
    }
];